earbuddy.net 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Earbuddy

Effective Date: 06/28/2017

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for ([Earbuddy](http://www.earbuddy.net/)). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about changes to Earbuddy.

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Cookies**

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site ([Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/start/#/?modal_active=none), [Sovrn](https://www.sovrn.com/), [Amazon](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/)). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Amazon Affliliates Program Disclosure**

Earbuddy is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to [Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/). This means that some of our links will redirect you to Amazon.com to purchase a product related to the link. Earbuddy receives a commission for purchases made through the following links.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address ([HERE](mailto:%20nick@earbuddy.net)):

See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
